Yuzu mitsumete nigamaya championship
I thought you were drawing your partner in a different way.
It's the easiest to draw.
I know.
Easiest to draw
happy
Hey, Hana-chan, you're always...
Yuzukin's illustrations will be drawn for me.
You draw me pretty.
Then I'm looking forward to it.
Looking forward to this one!
But you know what, guys?
And someone has to win a second time.
Yuzukin will win the championship.
Oh, no, no, no.
certainly
I'd say second place or something.
Yes, second place.
(esp. of men) one's prime (approx. age 30)
I wish you all the best.
I'll do my best.
Not coming out.
So I would like to have Moeko do it first.
Because Moeko and Yuuki are also very much in love with each other,
I kept looking next to him and thought, "I knew he would draw it pretty.
We have our own worlds.
It can be painted with a cute Yu.
Drawing a cute moeko in the role of Yu.
Drawing.
I'll try to paint a world of two people.
Start!
It's kinda cute when Moeko draws it right in front of you.
You're cute, though, with your mouth popped open and you're looking at me hard.
Oh, but it's good, good, good, good.
My mouth is open.
Good, good, good.
Okay, that's it.
End and start.
Keep it as it is, mouth.
What?
Keep the mouth keep it.
I don't want to.
Moeko drawing.
Our face, too.
My mouth will.
I feel like I'm with them, with the paintings.
After all, Yuko is, after all, a campus that can be painted pretty.
Campus.
Campus?
Eh, must be here.
By the way.
Come on, everyone.
An easy-to-see campus is kind of like doodling on a Yuko.
You're going to write to Yuko?
Isn't this it?
Draw it this way, this way.
Oh, it's not this way.
This way, this way, this way.
Here and there?
I know when I draw it over here.
Scary.
I don't know.
I would like to draw it properly over here.
Yo, start.
Yes, go ahead.
Oh!
10 seconds left.
Do it?
Cute.
Four, three, two, one, done!
Oh!
Scary.
Cute.
Cute, cute.
I wonder.
I knew it,
The material is good, you know.
Uh, uh, uh.
I'm writing twice.
It's easier to write,
I can't help it, here.
We're good at absorbing, SpongeBob,
It gets better.
SpongeBob, you say.
I don't want to talk anymore.
That's a sponge.
Grab a sense of what just happened,
I'm a fast absorber.
Yes, Haru-chan is pretty good the second time around.
It's a team spongy.
Team Spongy!
They don't know. I wish you the best of luck with your partner.
I'm looking forward to it. Well then, here's Hana-chan's challenge.
All right, let's get started!
Ah, but he was more polite than before.
I thought it was good earlier.
5 seconds ago 4
3 2
1 Finished!
Thank you for watching!
This way.
something that has been done (esp. constructions)
cute
I'm always dripping something.
You're dripping something.
My one mole on my nose, or something like that, is written around here.
It's gone up.
This nose is not thin.
Is that so? I didn't have time.
cute
Cute.
He asked me if she was pretty, and she didn't look anything like him.
Okay, here is the wish I drew. Ta-da!
Eh, cute!
I was surprised.
Super cute.
We're pretty much on the same page, aren't we?
It's about right.
Not good?
It's great.
Because it's cute with lots of blush on the sides.
Glad to hear it.
Pink.
I always wear blush darker.
We have made sure to portray that image properly in the features.
Yes.
The last one?
Looks like.
Not even close.
They look alike.
poor
Too cute.
Is it too cute?
This way.
Did Mizuki have that many bumps?
ribbon ribbon
Why did you put the ribbon on?
You put it there?
Is that it?
You put the ribbon there?
That's what I'm talking about, Mizuki.
It's a feeling or a leak.
I was in a hurry.
But isn't that a lot of lip smacking?
I've made up my mind! Who drew the most Ease-like self-portrait?
Wow!
No, I really wanted to make it Moeka. She's not this cute.
You're cute. This one looks the most like you, me. It certainly looks like you.
Please be prompt. Wah! I don't! You're so cute! If it were the most self-portrait or illustration, I would have wanted it to be Moeka, but it's cute and makes me happy,
I'd like to make a detergent, this one, of course. When I saw it, I thought to myself, "That looks a little like me.
I'm sorry to hear that. It's not about me.
Moyaka's Gazing Portrait Championship!
10 seconds left.
But, the mouth of a moyaka is very moyaka.